HOLIDAY SALE | SAVE 25-45% + FREE DELIVERY  
ORDER BY DEC 16 FOR CHRISTMAS DELIVERY

Menu

    * Back

    * Back

Galaxy Relaxation LLC Privacy Policy
====================================

Galaxy Relaxation LLC Privacy Policy
====================================

Effective 4/1/2021

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from [www.moonpod.co](http://www.moonpod.co/) (the “Site”). 

### PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT

When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information.”  
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:

  - “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).  
 - “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.  
 - “Web beacons,” “tags,” and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Text marketing (if applicable): With your permission, we may send text messages about our store, new products, and other updates. Updates include Checkout Reminders. Webhooks will be used to trigger the Checkout Reminders messaging system.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including credit card numbers), email address, and phone number.  We refer to this information as “Order Information.”

When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.

### HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices and/or order confirmations).  Additionally, we use this Order Information to:

Communicate with you;  
  
Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and  
  
When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).

### SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION

We share your Personal Information and Consumer Data, such as name, address, and transactional information with third parties and third-party marketing partners for commercial purposes.   For example, we use Shopify to power our online store--you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here:  [https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).  We also use Google Analytics to help us understand how our customers use the Site--you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here:  [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/).  You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here:  [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Upon inquiry, you are entitled to receive a copy of, amend, delete or erase, restrict the use of, or obtain an exportable copy of your Personal Data. To have access to your Personal Data data, please email us at cx@moonpod.co

The personally identifiable information that you provide to us and information about your order may be combined with other personally identifiable information (such as demographic information and past purchase history) available from our records and other sources. This information will be used to make our future marketing efforts more efficient. This information may also be shared with our third party service providers that assist us with our marketing efforts and with other marketers whose products or services we feel may be of interest to you. If you prefer that we do not share your name and address with other marketers, please email us at cx@moonpod.co.

Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

### BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING

As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you.  For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work](http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work).

You can opt out of targeted advertising by:  
FACEBOOK - [https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads)  
GOOGLE - [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous)  
BING - [https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at:  [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/).

### DO NOT TRACK

Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.  

### DATA RETENTION

When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.  

### CHANGES

We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.  

### CONTACT US

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at сx@moonpod.co.

\------------------------------------------------------------------------

Your cart
---------

Close

FREE SHIPPING ON ALL ORDERS

Your cart is empty

Subtotal:$0.00 USD

Loading...

Products
--------

Menu
----

Join The Super Moon Club
------------------------

Be first in line for discounts, updates, and to help us create our next product!

Email

 Subscribe  

Payment methods accepted

* American Express
* Apple Pay
* Diners Club
* Discover
* Google Pay
* Mastercard
* PayPal
* Shop Pay
* Venmo
* Visa

* * *

Copyright © 2022 [Moon Pod](https://www.moonpod.co/ "/")

Back

Choose options
--------------

Close

Close

Item added to your cart.
